<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Marriedbygen | Wedding Celebrant Blog</title>
        <link>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog</link>
        <description>Marriedbygen | Wedding Celebrant Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taylor & Morgan's Intimate Mountain Elopement]]></title>
            <link>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog/taylor-morgan-mountain-elopement</link>
            <guid>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog/taylor-morgan-mountain-elopement</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When we decided to elope, we knew we still wanted our ceremony to be special and meaningful. [Your Wife's Name] created an intimate experience that exceeded all our expectations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When we decided to elope, we knew we still wanted our ceremony to be special and meaningful. [Your Wife's Name] created an intimate experience that exceeded all our expectations.</p>
<p>Even though it was just the two of us (plus our photographers), [Your Wife's Name] put as much care and attention into our ceremony as she would for a large wedding. She helped us craft personal vows and suggested beautiful rituals that made our elopement feel sacred and significant.</p>
<p>What we appreciated most was [Your Wife's Name]'s flexibility and adventurous spirit. Our ceremony location required a short hike, and she was completely game for the adventure! Her calm presence and genuine joy for what she does made our day so special.</p>
<p>She even helped coordinate with our photographers to ensure all the important moments were captured perfectly. The ceremony she created for us was the perfect balance of meaningful, personal, and concise - exactly what we wanted for our elopement.</p>
<p>If you're planning an elopement or intimate ceremony, we can't recommend [Your Wife's Name] highly enough. She'll create a ceremony that feels true to you as a couple, regardless of the size or location.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <author>marriedbygen@gmail.com (Genevieve Berning)</author>
            <category>elopement</category>
            <category>outdoor ceremony</category>
            <category>intimate</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarah & Michael's Beach Wedding]]></title>
            <link>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog/sarah-michael-beach-wedding</link>
            <guid>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog/sarah-michael-beach-wedding</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We cannot thank [Your Wife's Name] enough for the beautiful ceremony she created for our beach wedding. From our first meeting, she took the time to truly understand our story and what was important to us.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We cannot thank [Your Wife's Name] enough for the beautiful ceremony she created for our beach wedding. From our first meeting, she took the time to truly understand our story and what was important to us.</p>
<p>The ceremony was everything we dreamed of and more. [Your Wife's Name] perfectly balanced heartfelt moments with touches of humor that reflected our relationship so well. Our guests kept commenting on how personal and meaningful the ceremony was.</p>
<p>What we appreciated most was how calm and organized [Your Wife's Name] was throughout the entire process. She guided us through writing our vows, helped us choose readings that resonated with us, and ensured everything ran smoothly on the day.</p>
<p>If you're looking for a celebrant who will create a ceremony that truly reflects who you are as a couple, we couldn't recommend [Your Wife's Name] more highly!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <author>marriedbygen@gmail.com (Genevieve Berning)</author>
            <category>beach wedding</category>
            <category>outdoor ceremony</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alex & Jordan's Celebration of Love]]></title>
            <link>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog/alex-jordan-garden-ceremony</link>
            <guid>https://nrob536.github.io/celebrant-website/blog/alex-jordan-garden-ceremony</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Finding the right celebrant was so important to us. We wanted someone who would honor our relationship and create a ceremony that felt authentic. [Your Wife's Name] exceeded our expectations in every way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Finding the right celebrant was so important to us. We wanted someone who would honor our relationship and create a ceremony that felt authentic. [Your Wife's Name] exceeded our expectations in every way.</p>
<p>From the moment we met [Your Wife's Name], we felt comfortable and heard. She was genuinely interested in our story and our vision for our ceremony. There was never a moment where we felt like we were working from a template - everything was created specifically for us.</p>
<p>[Your Wife's Name] was also incredible at incorporating elements that honored both our families and traditions while still keeping the ceremony focused on our commitment to each other. She found the perfect balance.</p>
<p>The ceremony itself was beautiful, moving, and joyful - exactly what we wanted. So many of our guests commented that it was the most personal and meaningful ceremony they'd ever attended.</p>
<p>We're so grateful to have found [Your Wife's Name] and can't recommend her highly enough to other couples.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <author>marriedbygen@gmail.com (Genevieve Berning)</author>
            <category>LGBTQ+</category>
            <category>garden ceremony</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>